{
    "bundles": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "title": "Modern Russian History", 
            "description": "Questions covering key dates, topics and issues of pre, post and communist Russia.",
            "questions": [
                {
                "id" : 1,
                "question": "What is the capital of the UK?",
                "answer": "London"
                },
                {
                "id" : 2,
                "question": "Why is Minecraft so great?",
                "answer": "Combination of freedom, simplicity and creativity in the game."
                },
                {
                "id" : 3,
                "question": "If you could be any animal, what animal would you be?",
                "answer": "Eagle"
                },
                {
                "id" : 4,
                "question": "What is my favourite genre of music?",
                "answer": "Jazz"
                },
                {
                "id" : 5,
                "question": "What's the real reason why people don't like Jazz?",
                "answer": "They fear it's lack of boundaries and structure."
                },
                {
                "id" : 6,
                "question": "What is the top Brexit Gezza?",
                "answer": "Dave"
                },
                {
                "id" : 7,
                "question": "What is IRN BRU?",
                "answer": "The best beverage to ever exist!"
                }
            ]
        },

        {
            "id": 2,
            "title": "Post-Modern Architectural Design", 
            "description": "Questions covering key dates, architects and styles of Post Modern style.",
            "questions": [
                 {
                "id" : 1,
                "question": "What is the capital of the UK?",
                "answer": "London"
                },
                {
                "id" : 2,
                "question": "Why is Minecraft so great?",
                "answer": "Combination of freedom, simplicity and creativity in the game."
                },
                {
                "id" : 3,
                "question": "If you could be any animal, what animal would you be?",
                "answer": "Eagle"
                },
                {
                "id" : 4,
                "question": "What is my favourite genre of music?",
                "answer": "Jazz"
                },
                {
                "id" : 5,
                "question": "What's the real reason why people don't like Jazz?",
                "answer": "They fear it's lack of boundaries and structure."
                },
                {
                "id" : 6,
                "question": "What is the top Brexit Gezza?",
                "answer": "Dave"
                },
                {
                "id" : 7,
                "question": "What is IRN BRU?",
                "answer": "The best beverage to ever exist!"
                }, 
                {
                    "id" : 8,
                    "question": "What is the capital of the UK?",
                    "answer": "London"
                    }
            ]            
        },

        {
            "id": 3,
            "title": "Post-War Expressionism", 
            "description": "Evalutaing European expressionism post WW2 in art, poetry and music.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the capital of the UK?",
                    "answer": "London"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Why is Minecraft so great?",
                    "answer": "Combination of freedom, simplicity and creativity in the game."
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "If you could be any animal, what animal would you be?",
                    "answer": "Eagle"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is my favourite genre of music?",
                    "answer": "Jazz"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What's the real reason why people don't like Jazz?",
                    "answer": "They fear it's lack of boundaries and structure."
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 6,
                    "question": "What is the top Brexit Gezza?",
                    "answer": "Dave"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 7,
                    "question": "What is IRN BRU?",
                    "answer": "The best beverage to ever exist!"
                    }
            ]
        },

        {
            "id": 4,
            "title": "Post-Modernity and Minecraft", 
            "description": "Revision concerning factual dates and information of the Minecraft series on Post-Modernity.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the capital of the UK?",
                    "answer": "London"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Why is Minecraft so great?",
                    "answer": "Combination of freedom, simplicity and creativity in the game."
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "If you could be any animal, what animal would you be?",
                    "answer": "Eagle"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is my favourite genre of music?",
                    "answer": "Jazz"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What's the real reason why people don't like Jazz?",
                    "answer": "They fear it's lack of boundaries and structure."
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 6,
                    "question": "What is the top Brexit Gezza?",
                    "answer": "Dave"
                    },
                    {
                    "id" : 7,
                    "question": "What is IRN BRU?",
                    "answer": "The best beverage to ever exist!"
                    }
            ]
        }

    ]
}